Hello, hello.
Top of the morning to you.
(EXCLAlMS)
Green M&M's.
Nature's Viagra.
Two of my favorite
joke areas combined.
lt's gonna be a good day.
l don't want to
bring my friends.
Why can't it
just be the two of us?
Because it's
St. Patrick's Day.
People go out in groups.
Well, why don't you
invite your friends?
Why are you being
so weird about this?
Stop fighting ! Just on
St. Patrick's Day, okay?
Just one
perfect day a year.
No hassles,
no problems, no kids.
Why no kids?
Yeah, where are your kids?
Nope. Uh-uh. Not today.
MlCHAEL: It is
St. Patrick's Day,
and here
in Scranton,
that is a huge deal.
lt is the closest
that the lrish will
ever get to Christmas.
(DOOR OPENS)
(EXCLAlMS)
ERlN: Welcome back, Dad.
Oh, thank you.
Hey.
KEVlN: Hey.
Hey!
ANDY: Welcome back, Tuna.
Hey.
DWlGHT: Very good.
Okay, we'll get back to you
on that right away. Thanks.
What do we got here?
Mega-desk.
Of course.
Command central.
Mmm-hmm.
Surveillance, gaming
and business.
Okay.
(SlGHS)
What? Come on. Jim !
Tweedledee and
Tweedle Dumbass
have been away
on maternity leave,
but now Tweedle Dumbass
is back and we have
a problem.
Yes, getting
hooked on mega-desk
was my own damn fault.
(SlGHS) I don't care
about assigning blame.
All I care about is mega-desk.
That is
all l care about.
Getting more mega-desk.
Oh, l love this.
So much fun.
There's such team spirit
in this room.
Morning, darling.
Morning.
Well, this is my last day
at the Scranton branch
for a while,
but I'm leaving it in
the very capable hands
of some of the
loveliest people I've ever
had the pleasure of knowing.
You know,
l'm gonna miss this place,
and the snow.
(LAUGHS) Do my dogs
love peeing in that snow!
Makes me think
they're onto something.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Oh, good morning,
sweetheart.
Good morning, honey pile.
l'm sorry,
but is that a gift
l see in your hands?
lt is.
This is a little
something for you
to remember your time here
in Scranton by.
ls that a lump of coal?
Yes, it is.
l haven't been that naughty.
No, no, no. That is
a good gift, actually.
Buildings here in Scranton
are literally powered by coal.
Uh. . . Thank you very much.
We don't
get much coal
down in Tallahassee.
l mean,
just alligators
and some of the worst
Chinese food you've
ever tasted.
Mmm, that sounds
great, actually.
Well, if you
ever get down in
my neck of the woods,
you got a place to stay.
MlCHAEL: When
you work for Sabre,
only one thing matters,
and l don't care
if you're a loser or
you practice bestiality,
if Jo likes you,
you are in.
And l am in.
Erin Go Bragh.
Andy "Go Bragh" to you.
Nice kilt.
Thanks.
lt's actually my sister's
old field hockey skirt.
Erin and l have
our first date tonight
and it has to be perfect.
Why? Because according
to How l Met Your Mother,
that's the date
that your kids are gonna
wait patiently to hear about,
and you better have
a good story for them.
Nope.
Great.
JlM: No.
Thank you.
No, no, no, no, no.
Come on. Come on.
Five more minutes.
Five more minutes
of mega-desk? Please?
ls this yours or mine?
They say that
no man is an island.
False. l am an island,
and this island is volcanic.
Mega-desk!
And it is about to erupt
with the molten hot lava
of strategy.
Good Lord.
l can't believe
l'm missing this.
PAM: It's kind of Iike
that lip thing she did
last night,
like a half-snarl,
haIf-smiIe.
I get the sense
that she's very ironic.
Okay. Love you.
We'll talk soon.
Must be amazing
being a father, right?
The miracle of life.
lt is. Big time.
Ah, that baby
is just discovering
a whole wide world right now.
lt's pretty amazing.
What up is, what down is,
who Mom is,
who Dad is.
Must be
tough being here
with all that going on.
lt's tough being here
for a lot of reasons.
l mean,
you're here at work
and the baby thinks that
the refrigerator is
its father.
ls that what
happened to you?
l'll tell you
what happened to me.
l didn't see my father for
the first two years of
my life.
l thought my mother
was my father and my
wet nurse was my mother.
And that's
a common mistake.
Turned out fine
for me. But Mose?
Oh, same story,
different ending.
(SNEEZlNG)
Hey, are you sick?
Oh, no, l'm fine. l just
have a little indigestion.
ln your nose?
Yes.
ERIN: l'm a little sick,
but I don't want to miss
my date with Andy.
l'll get better.
Whenever l'm sick
it goes away
within a few hours,
except once when
l was in the hospital
from age three to six.
Now, after all the talking
l've been doing,
it's your turn.
This is a town hall meeting.
l want to hear what y'all
sound like.
That is a great idea, J. B.
Thank you.
JO: You know,
l get way too many
ideas from the top.
Now, l want to
hear your ideas.
l mean,
did you guys know
that Liquid Paper,
that wasn't invented
by some fancy engineer.
No, that was created
by a lowly typist.
Oh, Jo, l have an idea
for suntan lotion soap.
You know,
it doesn't have
to be an invention.
l have a question.
Oscar, homosexual accountant.
ln the training manual,
it says that
there's a minority executive
training program
in Tallahassee.
l am so proud
of Sabre's Print ln
All Colors initiative.
Any Sabre employee of color
is welcome to apply, okay?
Darryl?
Darryl. Mellow, soulful,
smart for warehouse.
Okay, hush now.
Okay.
The Sabre
shipping method
could be more efficient.
Combining inventory systems
makes sense on paper,
but printers and paper
ship differently.
lt would be faster
to deliver them separately
instead of waiting
on everything to come in.
But you wouldn't need
more trucks? l mean. . .
Not at all.
There's a way
it can be scheduled.
l sketched
this out downstairs.
Well, look at you.
Look at that picture
that you drew.
Nice job.
We are very
proud of you.
You know what? We are
going to tape that up
on the refrigerator
in the kitchen.
(CLlCKS TONGUE)
l like this, Darryl.
l like this a lot.
Maybe you should be
doing your sketching upstairs.
Would you like
an office up here?
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Take Jim's old office.
Oh, l set my stuff
up in there.
So, just
give me a few minutes
to clean it out for you.
Yeah. l want to
hear more from you.
Absolutely.
All right.
Yeah, thank you.
Okay. Any questions?
Anything on anybody's mind?
l'm leaving tonight.
This is your last
chance for a while.
No! Say
it's not so, Jo!
We're gonna miss you.
We are gonna
miss you so much !
Don't go away!
Okay. Florida
ain't that far away.
Well, l'm heading
down there.
Well, anytime, now.
So, who. . .
How about
July 4th weekend?
Oh, honey,
you didn't buy a ticket.
l did.
Oh, honey,
l am not home very often,
and me and my relatives,
they take up the guest house.
l think you should
check with my office
before you book
any dates, okay?
You know what? ln the
spirit of full disclosure,
l have actually reserved
a bunch of different seats
on a bunch
of different flights,
but there are
a couple flights that
only have two tickets left,
so l think we should
pull the trigger. . .
Enough !
All right, everybody. Just
try to put a brave face on.
Let's follow
the chain of events.
Jo likes Michael,
Jo invites
Michael to house,
Jo doesn't like
Michael anymore.
Mmm.
(SlGHlNG)
Moving on up
To the east side
To a deluxe apartment
in the sky
Hello. l want you to stop
what you're doing right now.
You are stressed
and l am taking
you to lunch.
No, that's very
generous of you,
but l'm all set.
No is not an option.
Yes, it is.
All right, well,
if you need me, l'll be on
the other side of that wall.
Knock once for yes,
twice for no.
How many knocks
does it take to get
you to do some work?
(CHUCKLES)
Okay. l'll be over there.
And l'm actually pleased
to be able to offer you
printer cartridges and
toner now.
Jim.
Yeah.
Jim, sorry to bother you.
What?
My headphones are broken.
Right.
Can l listen to
my music at a low volume?
That's great. Great.
Okay.
Yeah.
The cat's in the cradIe
and the silver spoon
Little boy...
When was the last time
you updated your printer?
"When you coming home, Dad?"
"I don't know when"
No. You need to stop now.
We'll be together then, now
We're going to have
a good time then
Whether it's this time
or the next time.
(ANDY SlNGlNG)
(ANDY AND DWlGHT SlNGlNG)
The cat's in the cradIe
and the silver spoon
Little boy blue
and the man in the moon
No, we can definitely
talk about it. . .
You know what?
Can l call you back?
That'd be great. Thank you.
We'll be together then
We're going to have
a good time
No, l know l need
to work, l just. . .
l feel weird
not being home.
l am not surprised that
Dwight's using my baby
to steal my desk.
l'm a little surprised
that it's working.
This fax came for you.
(COUGHS)
Oh, no, no, no.
Are you feeling ill?
Oh, no, honey,
if you've got a bug,
l want you to go on home.
l can't have
you getting Callie
and Jo Junior sick.
These dogs have
gotta be in a commercial
with Dwight Howard next week.
Oh. No, l feel like
l could lift a car.
Yeah, but you sound
like death, girl.
Now, why don't
you go on home,
take care of yourself,
get in bed,
and shred that
and have them send me
a clean fax, all right?
Well. . .
ANDY: She shouId go home.
It's not the end of
the worId.
We'll go on
a date next week.
She's still going to
like me in a week, right?
Yes?
l was just working at my desk
and l wanted to run some new
leads by you.
Oh, you're sick.
(COUGHlNG)
Dang it.
That's exactly
why l sent that
receptionist home.
No, no, l'm not.
Getting everybody
sick in the office.
l have some
good ideas that. . .
l don't need any
heroes here, honey.
lt's time for you
to go on home now.
(SNEEZlNG) You sure?
Yeah.
You'll probably feel better
once you get some pants on.
Come on.
(CAR LOCK BEEPS)
Very nice.
Not bad, huh?
Real Hoop Dreams story
you got there.
Oh, man, you seem
to have caught Jo's eye.
How'd you make that happen?
l impressed her
with my good ideas.
(CHUCKLES SARCASTlCALLY)
Seriously. How did you do it?
l made a suggestion
at the meeting that
was good.
You were there.
How do l put
this delicately?
Does her family
owe your family something
in terms of a past injustice?
Now, Mike, l have
to ask you to leave
so that l can learn
about this tiny television.
Mmm, okay. All right.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
JO: Hey, there.
Hey, there.
So, l think l'm done.
Gonna head out,
unless you want to chat,
like we were doing earlier.
Well, there's chatting time
and there's working time,
and l'm still
on working time.
Mmm? Well, the clock
says chatting time, so. . .
Well, if you feel like
you've done a solid
day's work.
Right.
What?
Well, l mean,
if you can put
your name on this day
and be proud
of the amount of
work you've done,
then by all means,
you should toodle
on home.
Mmm. . .
Okay.
ls there
something else
l can help you with?
No, no, no,
that's super clear-ish.
Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope.
KEVlN: Just because
Jo has no Iife
does not mean that the
rest of us don't have lives.
Oscar has a life.
l think Ryan has
a life.
This is outrageous.
Hey, Pac-Man.
TODD: Hey, what's up,
Butt Plug?
How you doing, stud?
You're already there?
Dude, l've been
here since 3:00.
l've boot and
rallied twice.
How's the lady situation?
Fat and ugly.
You might actually
have a chance.
Oh, damn, that sounds great.
Unfortunately l am stuck here
because my boss is making us
work late.
Oh, here's what you do.
Hike up your skirt and
pull out your tampon,
borrow some balls
and come meet me.
Yeah, maybe next year.
Maybe next queer.
Hey, ladies,
who wants some
bangers and mash?
(PHONE LlNE DlSCONNECTS)
(SlGHS)
(RAlN PATTERlNG)
Oh, Andy!
Hi.
l'm in my jammy-jams.
That's okay.
l'm in my worky-works.
You look amazing.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Thanks.
Come in.
Okay.
Hey, me and Creed are in.
Are you guys in?
Oh, l'm in.
l'm in.
All right.
(DOOR OPENS)
JO: Oh, you don't become
the most powerful woman
in TaIIahassee
by slacking off.
(CHUCKLES)
You do it by working hard.
Or marrying rich.
l did both.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Got a little client meeting
at Shanny O'Gannigans tonight.
lt shouldn't
go all night long,
so if you'd like me to,
l can swing by your house
so the
baby can experience
a strong male presence.
No? Nothing?
Okay, have fun working.
(WHlSTLlNG)
Hi there, Jo.
Sorry to interrupt.
(PHONE RlNGlNG)
This evening l have. . .
Hello?
Hey, Jo, it's Jim Halpert.
l actually
scheduled a meeting at 7:30
with a very important client,
and it's so weird,
'cause we never have
meetings after 5:00 p.m. ,
but l was hoping
that maybe just this
once it would be okay.
Well, sure.
You know, you go ahead
and push some printers.
You know l will.
And by the way, seriously,
we never, never do this.
Okay.
All right.
Sorry, sugar.
What did you want?
Well, you see,
l actually do have
a meeting with a client.
l'm gonna just
reschedule for next week.
Thank you.
Thanks again,
by the way.
Hey, what are you
fellows doing up here?
We're here
to bust you out.
l wish, but l. . .
Dude, is your
shirt tucked in?
(COUGHS) Oh, yeah.
l must have did that
when l used the bathroom.
All right, then.
Let me get to it.
All right.
See you later.
(SlGHS)
(WOMAN CHATTERlNG ON TV)
Your hand's cold.
lt is? l'm sorry.
Yeah.
Have some more blanket.
Oh, thanks.
(EXCLAlMS)
What's up?
You're awake?
Andy, this is
my brother, Reed.
l didn't know
you had a brother.
He's my foster brother.
Well, any
brother of Erin's
is a friend of mine.
Nice to meet you.
Andy Bernard.
Cold hands.
Are we rotating seats or. . .
Yeah, you're the guest.
Go take the easy chair.
Best seat in the house.
Plus, you don't
have to sit next
to this big dork
and her smelly feet.
Hey. My feet aren't smelly.
They smell like roses.
Smell them.
(GROANS) Whoa.
(CHUCKLlNG)
So how does the whole
foster sibling thing work?
Do you guys
share one parent or. . .
None. We were
in the same house
from ages 1 0 to 1 2
and then from 1 5 to 1 8.
Right. Formative years.
Nice skirt.
lt's a kilt.
(MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Oh, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Yes, l am anxious
to get out of work,
but let me be clear,
it's not to celebrate
St. Patrick's Day.
lt's so
l can protest
St. Patrick's Day.
Overnight all
my damn bags home.
l'm carrying nothing
but my sable gloves.
l've had it with
Homeland Security.
And l want you to put all
those tracking numbers in
my BlackBerry.
How late are we
gonna work tonight?
You never know with Jo.
Sometimes we're here
until midnight,
sometimes she doesn't
show up for three days.
Why does she do that?
Why doesn't
she just tell you
what your schedule is?
Yeah. That'd be awesome.
l could get a girlfriend.
l wouldn't have
to go to Amsterdam
seven times a year.
But l'm young, right?
l will date when l'm dead.
(LAUGHlNG)
Do l really want
to turn out like Gabe?
Twenty-six, single,
tied to my desk,
no life, no family.
l want to have been married
by the time l would have
turned 30.
That's just. . .
That's just depressing.
Hello, Jo.
Anything l can do
for you, pudding?
There is,
as a matter of fact.
lt's getting sort of late.
lt's 8:30 and
it's St. Patrick's Day,
which is
a world ethnic holiday,
so l have decided
l'm going to dismiss
my employees.
Hmm.
l'm thrilled with the work
they've done today,
both the quality
and the quantity.
Great performance. Very,
very solid all the way around.
All right, then.
Okay. Happy St. Patrick's Day.
And also,
l would like to say
that l will be canceling
my trip down to Tallahassee,
although l do look forward
to our professional
relationship.
Michael?
Yes?
l look forward to that, too.
Oh.
lt's coming down out there.
Yes.
Thank you
for coming all the way here.
No, no. My pleasure.
l'm sorry l was so sick.
(BOTH CHUCKLlNG)
Great. Now l'm gonna get sick.
Excuse me! Excuse me!
Hey, guys, how are you?
(ALL LAUGHlNG)
Drinks are on me.
(ALL WHOOPlNG)
No, no, no, put your
credit cards away!
lt's on us.
(EXCLAlMS) All right!
MlCHAEL: Did I mess up
my career today
or my future
prospects at Sabre?
I don't know.
There is a chance, yes.
I'll tell you,
I love my job,
but Jo wants me
to put on a show for her
and pretend to work late?
Nah.
I spent
all day trying
to make her like me,
but I forgot to
ask myself something.
Do I even Iike her?
As the lrish poet
Bobby McFerrin said,
"Don't worry, be happy."
Whoops.
Okay. Okay. All right.
Best night ever.
What the hell is
going on back there?
JlM: Yeah. We should be
able to have that over
to you by Monday.
Yeah, no problem.
(CHUCKLlNG) Thank you.
What the hell is this?
Oh !
This is not mega-desk.
No, it's not.
They call it
"quad-desk."
That's ridiculous.
This is made up
of three desks.
Oh, my God.
We're gonna have to
rename it then,
aren't we?
(PHONE RlNGlNG)
Hello. Dwight Schrute.